Lurelle Guild Papers
Lurelle Guild Papers
- General files
  - Nedicks, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Leonard Nelson and Associates, Inc. (Box 13)
  - New business opportunities, 1950 - 1952 (Box 13)
  - New business
    - 1954 (Box 13)
    - 1956 (Box 13)
    - 1959 (Box 13)
    - 1961 (Box 13)
  - New business prospects, 1965 (Box 13)
  - New Geography of American Antiques, 1949 (Box 13)
  - New Haven Clock Company (Box 13)
  - New Haven Clock and Watch Company, 1948 (Box 13)
  - New Haven Railroad, 1 folder
    - 1936 - 1937 (Box 14)
    - 1938 - 1939 (Box 14)
    - 1945 (Box 14)
    - 1946, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Theodore A. Newhoff Advertising Agency
    - 1935 - 1936 (Box 14)
    - 1937 (Box 14)
    - 1943 (Box 14)
  - New materials (Box 14)
  - "New Office Look", 1956 (Box 14)
  - New office space, 1958 (Box 14)
  - New York Central, 1954 (Box 14)
  - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad
    - 1933 (Box 14)
    - 1944 (Box 14)
  - Nicholson, 1949 - 1954 (Box 14)
  - Norge (Box 14)
  - Norge Corporation (Box 14)
  - Notarized copy, 1964 (Box 14)
  - O
    - 1935 - 1936 (Box 14)
    - 1937 - 1939 (Box 14)
    - 1944 (Box 14)
    - 1945 (Box 14)
  - Office Lease, etc., 1958 (Box 14)
  - Oneida Community Ltd. (Box 14)
  - Orange Peel (Box 14)
  - Owens - Illnois Glass Company, 1932 - 1934 (Box 14)
  - Ox-Fibre Brush Company
    - 1937 - 1940 (Box 14)
    - 1941 (Box 14)
    - 1942 (Box 14)
    - 1948 - 1957 (Box 14)
    - 1963 (Box 14)
  - P
    - 1935 - 1936 (Box 14)
    - 1935 - 1940 (Box 14)
    - 1941 - 1943 (Box 14)
    - 1944 (Box 14)
    - 1945 (Box 14)
  - P.S.C.C. Layouts (Box 14)
  - Panama, 1955 (Box 14)
  - Pan American (Box 14)
  - Pan - American World Airways, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Pardee Tiles (Box 14)
  - Parrish, Amos and Company (Box 14)
  - Patents - disclosures (Box 14)
  - Paul - Tattar, 1962 (Box 15)
  - C.W. Paulson (Box 15)
  - Pennsylavania Railroad Company, 1932 (Box 15)
  - Permutit Company, 1 folder
    - 1936 (Box 15)
  - Pictorial, 1 folder
    - Manuscripts (Box 15)
    - Review, 1 folder (Box 15)
    - 1/36/[?] (Box 15)
  - Pinnacle Trade Mark (Box 15)
  - Pitney - Bowes, Inc., 1 folder (Box 15)
    - 1948 (Box 15)
    - 1949 (Box 15)
    - 1950 (Box 15)
    - 1954, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Plan and Zoning Commission, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Porter Steel Specialties, Inc. (Box 15)
  - W.E. Post, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Pressed Steel Car Company
    - 1940 (Box 15)
    - 1938 - 1940 (Box 15)
    - 1941 (Box 15)
    - 1942, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - 1943, March - June (Box 15)
    - 1943, July - Dec. (Box 15)
    - 1944 (Box 15)
    - 1945 (Box 15)
    - 1946 (Box 15)
    - 1945 - 1946 (Box 15)
  - Prestone Eveready (Box 15)
  - Preview (Box 15)
  - Priorities, 1945 - 1946 (Box 15)
  - Production Tooling Company, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Promotion (Box 15)
  - Publicity, 2 folders
    - Imperial (Box 15)
    - Imperial duplicates (Box 15)
    - International silver (Box 15)
    - Kensington, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Mohawk (Box 15)
    - Mohawk (Box 16)
    - Monsanto Chemical (Box 16)
    - Norge (Box 16)
    - Pictorial (Box 16)
    - Savafall (Box 16)
  - Publicity and speeches, 1949 - 1958 (Box 16)
  - Pullman Car and Manufacturing Company, 1931 - 1933 (Box 16)
  - Pyrene Manufacturing Company, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Q, 1944 (Box 16)
  - Quiet May (Box 16)
  - R
    - 1935 - 1936 (Box 16)
    - 1937 - 1940 (Box 16)
    - 1941 - 1943 (Box 16)
    - 1944 (Box 16)
    - 1945 (Box 16)
    - 1946 (Box 16)
  - RCA - Victor Division, 1953 (Box 16)
  - Radiant Heater Corporation, 1945 (Box 16)
  - Reeves, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1 folder
    - 1950 (Box 16)
    - 1951 (Box 16)
  - Remington Corporation
    - 1948 (Box 16)
    - 1946 - 1949 (Box 16)
    - 1950 (Box 16)
    - 1951 - 1953 (Box 16)
    - 1956 (Box 16)
    - 1959 (Box 16)
  - Rensie Watch Company (Box 16)
  - Reson and Williams, 1960 (Box 16)
  - Revall, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Revlon, 1958 - 1959; 1962 (Box 16)
  - Revlon Nail Clipper, 1962; 1964 (Box 16)
  - Richardson and Boynton (Box 16)
  - Risdon Manufacturing Company, 1 folder
    - 1936 - 1939 (Box 16)
    - 1944 (Box 16)
    - 1945 (Box 16)
    - 1946 (Box 16)
    - 1954 - 1962 (Box 16)
  - Roaster (Box 16)
  - Roberts, 1951 (Box 16)
  - Rodgers Advertising Agency (Box 16)
  - Roxalin Flexible Finishes, 1944 (Box 16)
  - Royal McBee, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Rubbermaid, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Rubbermaid, 1959 (Box 16)
  - Rushlight Club, 1960 (Box 16)
  - S
    - 1932 - 1936 (Box 17)
    - 1937 - 1940 (Box 17)
    - 1942 (Box 17)
    - 1943 (Box 17)
    - 1944 (Box 17)
    - 1945 (Box 17)
    - 1946 - 1947 (Box 17)
  - Sack Incorporated (Box 17)
  - Sales Exec. Club, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Salisbury Brothers Furniture Company (Box 17)
  - Salz Bros. (Box 17)
  - Schick Electric Inc., 1 folder
    - 1956 (Box 17)
  - F. Schumacher and Company, 1 folder
    - 1944 - 1946 (Box 17)
    - 1959 (Box 17)
  - Isabel Scott (Box 17)
  - Scranton Corp., 1 folder
    - 1963 (Box 17)
  - Scranton Lace Company, 2 folders
    - 1954 (Box 17)
  - Seaboard AirLine Railway, 1945 (Box 17)
  - Seaboard AirLine Railway, 1946 (Box 17)
  - Seagram's, 1957 (Box 17)
  - J.P. Seeburg Corporation, 1944
  - J.P. Seeburg Corporation, 1945 - 1947
  - Servel Incorporated (Electrolux)
    - 1934 - 1936 (Box 17)
    - 1937 - 1939 (Box 17)
    - 1937 - 1940 (Box 17)
    - 1940, Servel Product Improvement Surveys (Box 17)
    - 1941 (Box 17)
    - 1942 (Box 17)
    - 1943, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - 1944 (Box 17)
    - 1945 (Box 17)
    - 1946 (Box 17)
    - 1945 - 1946, Servel Gas Stove (Box 17)
    - 1948 (Box 17)
    - 1949 (Box 17)
    - 1950 - 1951 (Box 17)
  - Sewing kits, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Sheer, H.M. Company (Box 18)
  - Simmons, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Singer Company, 1 folder
    - 1933 - 1934 (Box 18)
    - 1964, Decorating Contest (Box 18)
    - 1965, Climate Control Division (Box 18)
    - 1965, Correspondence (Box 18)
    - 1966, Drapes Project (Box 18)
    - 1966 (Box 18)
  - Society of Industrial Designers, 1 folder
    - 1945 (Box 18)
    - 1946 (Box 18)
    - 1951 (Box 18)
  - Solo Products
    - 1947 - 1943 (Box 18)
    - 1951 (Box 18)
    - 1951 (Box 18)
  - Solomon Carnet, 1962 (Box 18)
  - A.G. Spalding and Brothers, Inc.
    - 1943 (Box 18)
    - 1944 (Box 18)
    - 1945 (Box 18)
    - 1946 (Box 18)
  - Speakman Company, 1931 - 1933 (Box 18)
  - John A. Spooner, 1958; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Springweiler, 1958 (Box 18)
  - Stamford Wall Paper Company, 1941 - 1943 (Box 18)
  - Stamps
    - Canada (Box 18)
    - Canal Zone and Dominican Republic (Box 18)
    - Drawings (Box 18)
    - Information (Box 18)
    - Italy (Box 18)
    - Netherland (Box 18)
    - Norway (Box 18)
    - Philippine Documentary Stamp (Box 18)
    - South America (Box 18)
    - United Nations (Box 19)
    - United States Internal Revenue (Box 19)
  - Standard Brands, 1935 - 1936 (Box 19)
  - Stanley Home Products, 1954 - 1955 (Box 19)
  - Stanley Works, 1956 - 1957 (Box 19)
  - J.P. Stevens, 1946 (Box 19)
  - J.P. Stevens, 1948 - 1951 (Box 19)
  - Stewart - Warner Corporation, 1932 - 1935 (Box 19)
  - Stolen Figurehead, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Stolen Statue, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Studebaker Corporation (Box 19)
  - Sylvania Electric Company, 1 folder
    - 1943 (Box 19)
    - 1944 (Box 19)
    - 1945 (Box 19)
    - 1946 (Box 19)
    - 1948 (Box 19)
    - 1949 (Box 19)
    - 1950 (Box 19)
    - 1949 - 1950 (Box 19)
    - 1957 - 1958, 1963 (Box 19)
    - 1966 (Box 19)
  - Syracuse University Financial Summary (Box 19)
  - T
    - 1932 - 1936 (Box 19)
    - 1937 - 1940 (Box 19)
    - 1944 (Box 19)
    - 1945 (Box 19)
    - 1945 - 1946 (Box 19)
  - Tatter, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Tel - autograph, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Textron Inc., 1944 (Box 19)
  - Textron Inc., 1945 (Box 19)
  - Thompson, J. Walter (Box 19)
  - Timkin Axles, 1943 - 1944 (Box 19)
  - To be answered (Box 19)
  - Town, Plan and Zoning Commission (Box 20)
  - Towne House, 1956 (Box 20)
  - Trenton Potteries Company (Box 20)
  - True Temper, 1954 - 1955 (Box 20)
  - True Temper, 1964 (Box 20)
  - U, 1 folder
    - 1935 - 1936 (Box 20)
    - 1944 (Box 20)
    - 1945 (Box 20)
    - 1945 - 1946 (Box 20)
  - Underwood Elliot Fisher Company, 1 folder
    - 1934 - 1936 (Box 20)
    - 1937 - 1940 (Box 20)
    - 1941 (Box 20)
    - 1942 (Box 20)
    - 1943 (Box 20)
    - 1944 (Box 20)
    - 1945 (Box 20)
    - 1946 (Box 20)
    - 1948 (Box 20)
    - 1949 (Box 20)
    - 1950 (Box 20)
    - 1951 (Box 20)
    - 1952 (Box 20)
    - 1954 (Box 20)
  - Union Carbide, 1964 (Box 20)
  - The Union News Company, 1948 (Box 20)
  - The Union New Company, 1949 - 1950 (Box 20)
  - United AirLines, 1965 (Box 20)
  - United Oil Products, 1967 (Box 20)
  - United States Rubber, 1958 - 1959 (Box 20)
  - V, 1 folder (Box 20)
    - 1944 (Box 20)
    - 1945 (Box 20)
    - 1945 - 1946 (Box 20)
  - Wm. Van Buran, 1949 (Box 20)
  - Wm. Van Buran, 1950 - 1951 (Box 20)
  - Vanity Fair Mills, Inc., 1965 - 1967 (Box 20)
  - Viosca (Box 20)
  - Virginia - Lincoln Furniture Corporation (Box 20)
  - W
    - 1935 - 1936 (Box 20)
    - 1937 (Box 20)
    - 1944 (Box 20)
    - 1945 (Box 20)
    - 1945 - 1946 (Box 20)
  - Waite Carpet Company (Box 20)
  - Walker and Pratt Manufacturing Company, 1936 (Box 20)
  - Walker Kidde and Company (Box 20)
  - Warren Telechron Company (Box 20)
  - Ralph Watts, 1 folder
    - 1958 (Box 20)
  - Wear - Ever, 1 folder
    - 1935 (Box 20)
    - 1936 (Box 20)
    - 1959 (Box 21)
    - 1960 (Box 21)
    - 1960 - 1962 (Box 21)
    - 1958 - 1962 (Box 21)
    - 1965 (Box 21)
    - 1966 (Box 21)
    - 1965 - 1968 (Box 21)
  - Westinghouse, 3 folders
    - TV (Box 21)
    - 1931 - 1936 (Box 21)
    - 1944 (Box 21)
    - 1945, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - 1946 (Box 21)
    - 1948, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - 1949, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - 1950 (Box 21)
    - 1951 - 1952 (Box 21)
    - 1953, 1 folders
      - Coffee - maker - survey (Box 21)
      - Perl House (Box 22)
    - 1954, 1 folder
      - Massachusetts (Box 22)
      - Ohio (Box 22)
    - 1953 - 1954 (Box 22)
    - 1955, 1 folder
      - Belt (Box 22)
    - 1957 (Box 22)
    - 1960 - 1962 (Box 22)
    - 1963, Clock Market Report (Box 22)
    - 1963, Mirrors and hotel and motel equipment (Box 22)
    - 1962 - 1963 (Box 22)
    - 1964, Portable refrigerator; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - 1965, Things to be done (Box 22)
    - 1964 - 1965, 1 folder
      - Steam Grille - portable dishwasher (Box 22)
    - 1967, Sargeant (Box 22)
  - Westmoreland Glass Company
    - 1939 - 1940 (Box 22)
    - 1941 (Box 22)
    - 1958 - 1959 (Box 22)
  - Weston Electrical Instrument Corporation
    - 1935 - 1936 (Box 22)
    - 1937 - 1939 (Box 22)
  - Wham - O - Company (Box 22)
  - A.C. White Duplicates (Box 22)
  - H.C. White, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - William C. White (Box 22)
  - Mrs. William White, 1949 (Box 22)
  - Whiting, 1954 (Box 22)
  - Whitney Chain Company, 1950 (Box 22)
  - Whitney, F.A. Carriage Company (Box 22)
  - Mrs. Williams (Box 22)
  - Williamsburg (Box 22)
  - Wood - Austin, 1959 (Box 22)
  - Wood - Nicholas (Box 22)
  - Wood Office Furniture Institute
    - 1943 (Box 22)
    - 1944 (Box 22)
  - Wood - Richardson
    - 1959 - 1960 (Box 22)
    - Germany, 1 folder
      - 1952 - 1953 (Box 22)
  - Wooster Rubber Company
    - 1938 - 1940 (Box 22)
    - 1951 - 1953 (Box 22)
    - 1956 - 1958 (Box 22)
  - World - Telegram (Box 22)
  - Helen Worth, 1964; MOLD FOUND IN THE FOLDERS OF THIS BOX
  - Alcoa Steamship, 2 folders
    - 1948 (Box 23)
    - 1949 (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
  - XYZ
    - 1938 - 1940 (Box 24)
    - 1945 (Box 24)
    - 1945 - 1946 (Box 24)
    - 1947 (Box 24)
  - Young and Rubicam, Incorporated (Box 24)
  - Zenith Machine Company (Box 24)
- Financial records
  - Advertising (Box 24)
  - Airline flights (Box 24)
  - Bank statements and cancelled checks
    - Bank of Bermuda
      - 1959 - 1962, Dollar account (Box 24)
      - 1963, Dollar account (Box 24)
      - 1963, Sterling account (Box 24)
    - Bank of N.T. Butterfield and Son, Limited, 1963 (Box 24)
    - Chase National Bank
      - 1935 - 1938, 1941, 1943 - 1946, 1948 - 1950 (Box 24)
    - Chase National Bank
      - 1950 - 1954, 1956, 1957 (Box 25)
    - Fifth Avenue Bank of New York, 1935 (Box 25)
    - Bank of New York (Box 25)
  - Bills, 3 folders
    - M. Aaronson (Box 25)
    - Alcoa
      - Due bill (Box 25)
      - Preliminary work, 1953 - 1955 (Box 25)
    - Presentation, 1955 (Box 26)
    - Purchase orders and invoices (Box 26)
    - Time sheets
      - 1950 - 1953, 3 folders (Box 26)
  - Alcoa Steamship
    - Invoice listing and items (Box 26)
    - 1955, Mr. and Mrs. Green (Box 26)
    - Paramaribo
      - Purchase order (Box 26)
      - Shipped (Box 26)
      - 1954 - 1957, Worksheets (Box 26)
    - 1955 - 1960, 1962 (Box 26)
  - Aluminum Company of America, 1942 (Box 26)
  - Aluminum Cooking Utensil Co., 1940 (Box 26)
  - Armentrout, 1955 - 1956; 1964 - 1965 (Box 26)
  - Becton, Dickinson, and Co., 1938 (Box 26)
  - B.S.F., 1962 (Box 26)
  - Billhardt Residence, 1960 (Box 26)
  - Bills, 1935 - 1943 (Box 26)
  - Bills and miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Bills receivable to, 1934 (Box 26)
  - Bills to be sent out (Box 26)
  - Bills to be sent out to clients, 1941 - 1944 (Box 26)
  - Bird and Son, Inc., 1941 (Box 26)
  - Carrier
    - 1952 - 1955, Statements (Box 26)
    - 1953 - 1957 (Box 26)
    - 1956 - 1957, Monrovia, California (Box 26)
  - Chase National Bank Deposit Slips, 1949 (Box 26)
  - Chase National Bank Deposit Slips, 1950 (Box 26)
  - Corsiar, 1958 - 1959 (Box 26)
  - Crown, 1953 - 1956 (Box 26)
  - Duplicate bills (Box 26)
  - Elastic Stop Nut Corporation, 1943 (Box 26)
  - Electrolux, 1950 - 1965 (Box 26)
  - Electrolux to, 1965 (Box 27)
  - Expense slips (Box 27)
  - Gasoline auto bills, 1962 - 1963 (Box 27)
  - Guild, personal (Box 27)
  - L. Guild trips (Box 27)
  - Hyland and Gregory, 1951 (Box 27)
  - Industrial displays (Box 27)
  - Invoices to be charged, 1951 (Box 27)
  - Johns Manville bills, 1938 - 1939 (Box 27)
  - Kensington, 1 folder
    - Bills (Box 27)
    - Bills and royalties, 1 folder
      - 1941 - 1943 (Box 27)
    - Statements, 1950 - 1958 (Box 27)
  - Ledgers
    - 1938 - 1942 (Oversize 2)
    - 1939 - 1946 (Oversize 2)
    - 1936 - 1938 (Oversize 2)
    - 1935 - 1936, 1938 (Oversize 2)
  - New Haven ... old bill material (Box 27)
  - New Haven Railroad, 1949; 1953,; 1956 (Box 27)
  - Ox - Fibre Bills, 1941 - 1943 (Box 27)
  - Pitney Bowes, 1952 - 1953 (Box 27)
  - Pitney Bowes, 1956 (Box 27)
  - Pressed Steel Car Co., 1945 - 1946 (Box 27)
  - Receipts, 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Royalty statements (Box 27)
  - Rubbermaid, Inc., 1958 (Box 27)
  - Sargeant, 1953 (Box 28)
  - Sargeant furnishings, 1962 (Box 28)
  - Schick bills, 1956 - 1957 (Box 28)
  - Schumacher (Box 28)
  - Scranton Lace - statements, 1944 - 1952 (Box 28)
  - Servel bills (Box 28)
  - Store receipts (Box 28)
  - Time records (Box 28)
  - Trips, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - True temper, 1957 (Box 28)
  - Underwood statements (Box 28)
  - Wearever Aluminum
    - 1947 - 1956, 1958 (Box 28)
    - 1957 - 1960 (Box 28)
    - 1961 - 1962, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Westinghouse
    - 1955 (Box 28)
    - 1962 - 1965, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Paid bills, 3 folders
    - Alcoa (Box 28)
    - 1938 (Box 28)
    - 1940, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - 1940 (Box 29)
    - 1941, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - 1942, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - 1943, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - 1946 (Box 29)
    - 1947, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - 1948, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - 1949 (Box 30)
    - 1950, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - 1951 (Box 30)
    - 1952, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - 1953, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - 1954, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - 1955 (Box 30)
    - 1955 (Box 31)
    - 1956, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 1957, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 1958, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 1959, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 1960, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - 1961 (Box 31)
    - 1961 (Box 32)
    - 1962, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - 1961 - 1962, Wearever (Box 32)
    - 1963, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - 1964, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - 1965, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Certified public accountant's reports, 1936; 1937 (Box 32)
  - Checkbooks (Box 32)
  - Chase National Bank of the City of New York, 1935 - 1943; 12 vols. (Box 32)
  - Chase National Bank of the City of New York, 1941 - 1945; 6 vols. (Box 33)
  - Fifth Avenue Bank of New York
    - 1932 - 1933, 2 vols. (Box 33)
    - 1933 - 1935, 7 vols. (Box 33)
    - 1 Empty bankbook (Box 33)
    - 1935, 1 vol. (Box 33)
  - Correspondence, 1936 - 1941; 1943,; 1955 - 1958 (Box 34)
  - Insurance (Box 34)
  - Leases (Box 34)
  - Journals
    - Petty cash, 1932 - 1937 (Box 34)
    - Work trips, 1933 - 1937 (Box 34)
  - Magazine subscriptions, 1951 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 34)
  - Petty cash
    - 1937 (Box 34)
    - 1938 (Box 34)
    - 1937 - 1938 (Box 34)
    - 1940 - 1942 (Box 34)
    - 1953 (Box 34)
    - 1954, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 1955, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 1956 (Box 35)
    - 1957 (Box 35)
    - 1958 (Box 35)
    - 1959 (Box 35)
    - 1960 (Box 35)
    - 1961 (Box 35)
    - 1962 (Box 35)
    - 1963 (Box 35)
    - 1964 (Box 35)
    - 1965 (Box 35)
  - Taxes (Box 35)
  - Taxes and miscellaneous, 1930; 1935 - 1937 (Box 35)
  - Taxes and miscellaneous, 1938 - 1939 (Box 35)
  - Taxes and miscellaneous, 1940 - 1943 (Box 36)
- Shop drawings
  - Alcoa Aluminum Building - Pittsburgh, 4 folders (Box 36)
  - Alcoa Aluminum Company, bldg. plans, 1950s (Oversize 3)
  - Alcoa Steamship Company, 2 folders
    - Development (Box 36)
    - 1946, Lamps (Box 36)
    - 1946, main deck (Box 36)
    - 1947 - 1948, Offices and houses (Box 36)
    - 1950 (Box 36)
  - Aluminum Company of America, 4 folders (Box 36)
  - Aluminum Company of America
    - Museum, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Pittsburgh Building (Box 37)
    - 1946 (Box 37)
    - 1948 (Box 37)
    - 1950, Offices (Box 37)
    - 1950 - 1952, Wearever (Box 37)
  - Aluminum Cooking Utensil Company, 4 folders
    - 1946 (Box 37)
    - 1950, Wearever (Box 37)
  - American District Telegraph, 1 folder (Box 37)
  - American Druggist, 1946 - 1950; Magazine (Box 37)
  - American Locomotive Company, 1945 (Box 37)
  - Fred Atkins, 1950 - [?] (Box 37)
  - Atwater - kent Company (Box 37)
  - N.W. Ayer
    - American Rolling Mills (Box 37)
    - 1946, Masonite; 2 folders (Box 37)
  - B (Box 37)
  - Mr. Baird's Apartment (Box 37)
  - Bates (Box 37)
  - Becton Dickinson Company, 1946 - 1950 (Box 37)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Billhardt's Residence (Box 37)
  - Bird and Son, 1 folder
    - 1936 (Box 37)
  - Bourgois, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Bourgois, 1946 - 1948 (Box 38)
  - Charles T. Brandt, 1946 - 1950 (Box 38)
  - Building notices (Box 38)
  - Burke (Box 38)
  - Car lighting (Box 38)
  - Phillip Carey Manufacturing Company, 1946 (Box 38)
  - Phillip Carey Manufacturing Company, 1946 - 1950 (Box 38)
  - Carrier Corporation, 2 folders
    - 1944 (Box 38)
    - 1945 (Box 38)
    - 1946, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - 1947 - 1952 (Box 38)
  - Carrier Engineering Corporation
    - Air conditioning (Box 39)
    - Heating compressors (Box 39)
    - Heater, 1956 - 1957 (Box 39)
  - Century Stove (Box 39)
  - Certain - Teed (Box 39)
  - Chase Brass and Copper Company, 7 folders
    - Lights (Box 39)
  - C.F. Church Manufacturing Company (Box 39)
  - Colonial Radio Corporation, 1945 (Box 39)
  - Columbia Mills, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Connecticut Electric Sales Company (Box 39)
  - Continental Can Company, 1958 - 1959; 1963 (Box 39)
  - Al Cook, 1952 - 1954 (Box 39)
  - Corning Glass Works (Box 39)
  - Corning Glass Works (Box 40)
  - Crowell Publishing Co. (Box 40)
  - Crown (Box 40)
  - Crystal Room, 1949 (Box 40)
  - R.E. Dietz (Box 40)
  - J.C. Dillon Company, 1947; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Dime Savings Bank, 1950 (Box 40)
  - Dish Plans (Box 40)
  - Dixie Cup Company
    - 1945 (Box 40)
    - 1946 (Box 40)
    - 1946 - 1950 (Box 40)
  - Douglas House, 1949 - 1950 (Box 40)
  - Durstine Agency for Seagram Advertising, 1946 - 1950 (Box 40)
  - Edwards, 1946 - 1950 (Box 40)
  - Edwards Manufacturing Company
    - 1945 (Box 40)
    - 1946 (Box 40)
    - 1946 - 1947 (Box 40)
  - Edy Plastics (Box 40)
  - Elastic Stop Nut Corporation, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Electrolux Corporation
    - 1945 (Box 40)
    - 1946 (Box 40)
  - Electrolux, Incorporated, 1946 - 1950 (Box 41)
  - Electrolux, 1947 (Box 41)
  - Emery (Box 41)
  - Federal Housing Authority, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Fluted Gundersen Glass (Box 41)
  - Fosteria Glass Company, 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Fram Corporation (Box 41)
  - Freydberg Brothers Strauss, 1945 (Box 41)
  - Freydberg Brothers Strauss, 1946 - 1950 (Box 41)
  - Frisby - (House of Frisby) (Box 41)
  - Fuller, Smith and Ross, 1947 (Box 41)
  - Mr. Garrett, 1 folder
    - 1946 - 1950 (Box 41)
  - Garton Toy Company (Box 41)
  - Garton Toy Company (oversize) (Oversize 12)
  - General Electric, 3 folders (Box 41)
  - General Fireproofing, 1945 (Box 41)
  - General Stokers, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Goblin Electric Cleaner Company, 1946 - 1950 (Box 41)
  - Goblin Vacuum Cleaner Company, 1945 (Box 41)
  - Gold Medal Folding Furniture Company (Box 42)
  - Grable (Box 42)
  - Grable House, 1955 (Box 42)
  - Great American Industries, 1946 (Box 42)
  - Phonograph, 1946 (Box 42)
  - Greif, 1946 - 1950 (Box 42)
  - Greyhound Bus Company, 1945 (Box 42)
  - Griswold Manufacturing Company (Box 42)
  - Guild, L.V.A., 1946 - 1950; Personal (Box 42)
  - Guild Associates
    - Drawings (Box 42)
    - Office plans, 1946 - 1950 (Box 42)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Hamilton Manufacturing Company (Box 42)
  - H.J. Heinz Company (Box 42)
  - Andrew B. Hendryx Company, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Hershey Manufacturing Company, 1947 (Box 42)
  - Holcomb and Hoke (Box 42)
  - Howe Scale Company, 1945 (Box 42)
  - Hurley Machine, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Huyler's, 1950 (Box 42)
  - Industrial Food Crafts, Inc., 1946; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Ingersol - Waterbury Company, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - International Business Machine (Box 42)
  - International Silver, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Johns Manville Corporation, 1 folder
    - World's Fair (Box 42)
    - 1942 - 1943 (Box 42)
  - David Kahn, Inc. (Box 43)
  - David Kahn Company, 1946 (Box 43)
  - Kayser Remington Display (Box 43)
  - Julius Kayser
    - Store front #1 (Box 43)
    - Store front #2 (Box 43)
    - Store front #3 (Box 43)
    - Montreal show room, 1947 (Box 43)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 43)
    - Canada show room, 1948 (Box 43)
    - Chicago show room, 1948 (Box 43)
    - 1948 (Box 43)
  - Kensington, 7 folders
    - Bent glass (Box 43)
    - Card games accessories (Box 43)
    - Dishware (Box 43)
    - Drawings, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Showroom, display pieces, working charts, etc (Box 43)
    - Silk screen designs and bent glass, 1945 (Box 43)
    - 1946 (furniture) (Box 44)
    - 1946, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - 1947, showroom (Box 44)
    - 1947 (Box 44)
    - 1948 (Box 44)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 44)
    - 1948, 1950 (Box 44)
  - Kins Ware, 1950 (Box 44)
  - Walter Kidde Co. (Box 44)
  - Kittinger Company, 5 folders (Box 44)
  - H.M. Kolbe, 1946; 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Kolbe, 1947 (Box 44)
  - Kroehler (Box 44)
  - Kron Company, 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Laundromat (Box 44)
  - Libby Glass (Box 44)
  - McDonald Company (dishwasher) (Box 44)
  - Manning, Maxwell and Moore (Box 45)
  - Masonite train interior, 1946 (Box 45)
  - Charles H. Mayne (Box 45)
  - May Oil Burner Company, 3 folders (Box 45)
  - Miller Metal Products Company, 1946-1950 (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous, 10 folders (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous, 7 folders (Box 47)
  - Miscellaneous, 9 folders (Box 48)
  - Miscellaneous, 8 folders (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous, 12 folders (Box 50)
  - Miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 51)
  - Miscellaneous, 1946 - 1950; 1 folder (Box 51)
  - Mohawk, 1945 (Box 51)
  - Mohawk Carpet and Furniture (oversize) (Oversize 12)
  - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1946 (Box 51)